<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tim Jarzombek</title><link>https://jarz.net/</link><description>Recent content on Tim Jarzombek</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 20:54:18 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jarz.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Azure Application Insights payload logging in ASP.NET Core 3.1</title><link>https://jarz.net/posts/app-insights-logging-middleware/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 20:54:18 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://jarz.net/posts/app-insights-logging-middleware/</guid><description>At the beginning of January I presented on Azure Application Insights at CodeMash. While building my demo against an ASP.NET Core 3.1 project, I couldn't reuse an existing TelemetryInitializer to log request bodies for troubleshooting. A TelemetryInitializer allows developers to add or modify properties on telemetry sent to Application Insights; Microsoft's example overrides the default success logic such that 400-level errors aren't considered failures (the default in Application Insights). Changes made in ASP.</description></item><item><title>About Tim</title><link>https://jarz.net/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jarz.net/about/</guid><description>Tim Jarzombek is an experienced software developer living in Indianapolis, Indiana. His primary development interests are RESTful API development, secure development practices, and DevOps tools.
Development Experience Tim has worked with these languages and technologies:
Primary stack: C#, ASP.NET Core, SQL Server, Angular CI/CD: Azure DevOps, Team Foundation Server, Jenkins Android: Java, Android Studio, Jenkins build &amp;amp; deploy pipelines iOS: Objective-C, XCode, fastlane.tools, Jenkins build &amp;amp; deploy pipelines</description></item><item><title>Speaking</title><link>https://jarz.net/speaking/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jarz.net/speaking/</guid><description>Previous Conference Date Location Title CodeMash January 7 - 10, 2020 Sandusky, OH +5, Insightful: Azure Application Insights to improve your code</description></item></channel></rss>